Hello everyone.
Everyone can hear me. Can you raise your
hand if you can hear me properly? Thank
you very much. Right now
I'll welcome you with an interesting
fact. Did you know that you can speak at
around 170 words per minute while your
typing abilities
>> Hello.
>> Hi Dylan. How's it going?
>> Uh it's doing fine. How about you?
>> How about you? Hey, I just uh could use
some help for this whole transcription
thing because yeah, you did dictation
feature. So, could you please come on
stage and help me present it?
>> Yeah, sure. Coming right up.
>> Right off,
>> ladies and gentlemen, Dylan.
>> Quick uh quick demo before we jump into
actual dictation.
>> Yep. Uh we just took a phone call and
with new sets of feature new new set of
transcription features you can now open
your phone app
open your phone call and you can see
both full transcript as well as the
summary. So you can quickly skim on the
on the phone uh phone list view for
where's your actual call and you can
click on it to see the details. Now
let's go back to our presentation as we
are finally uh complete.
>> Yeah. So transcribe your meetings in no
time. Now within version this 19 of UDO
you can transcribe whatever uh you need.
So meetings um voice calls or even
videos directly within ODO and within
any HTML field and all of that is done
in real time. As you can see on screen
right now is the new transcription
component which can be used in any HTML
field and you can see a snippet of how
it looks like like with the timestamps
and all the transcription features uh of
the agent.
Then you can with this component you can
take a bunch of notes that will be used
directly as a context for the
transcription. This is mainly useful for
the transcript to be able to grasp if
you have specific concepts for let's say
a meeting a very technical meeting so
that the transcription understands what
uh your context is about and can do
proper transcript.
Then you when you're finished speaking
the the app automatically takes the
whole transcripts of the recording and
uh makes a summary that you can see
here. This summary can be modified uh
with the editor itself or you can also
click one of the quick action buttons
that will be used to replace the current
summary and uh update it accordingly.
And lastly, you also have the
possibility to directly share the
summary of your meeting through the mail
composer within Odu. And this will be